(Sheldon:)It'll take two weeks.
(Penny:)Leonard, are you okay?
(Leonard:)Um, I'm not sure.
(Howard:)What's going on?
(Leonard:)Well, Mrs. Latham said
she was seriously considering
(Leonard:)donating money so we could get
a cryogenic centrifugal pump...
(Howard:)Yes!
Oh, wow!
(Leonard:)...then she stuck
her tongue down my throat.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Penny:)Okay, we can't keep
explaining everything.
(Penny:)Read that book
we got you.
(Leonard:)She hit on me.
(Howard:)Wait-wait-wait.
Are you telling us
(Howard:)that old lady wanted
to have sex with you
(Howard:)in exchange for giving your
department millions of dollars?
(Leonard:)I think so.
(Howard:)You lucky duck.
(Penny:)You're really
a broken toy, aren't you?
(Leonard:)I was able to get out of there
before anything else happened,
(Leonard:)but she wants to see me again
tomorrow night.
(Mrs Latham:)Excellent!
What are you planning to wear?
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)Penny, you're an expert on trading
sexual favors for material gain--
(Sheldon:)walk him through this.
(Leonard:)Well, n-no, hold on a second,
I'm not going to sleep with her.